翻译：申导（CST认证敏捷教练）
ever since computers were invented，they've
自从计算机被发明以来，
really just been glorified calculators machines
实际上它们只是被美化的计算器机器，
that execute the exact instructions
可以执行
given to them by the programmers
程序员给出的精确指令
but something incredible is
但令人难以置信的事情正在发生，
happening now computers have started
现在计算机已经开始
gaining the ability to learn and think
获得像我们一样学习、思考
and communicate just like we do they can
和交流的能力
do creative intellectual work that
他们可以做
previously only humans could do we call
以前只有人类才能做的创造性智力工作
this technology generative AI and you
我们称之为生成人工智能
may have encountered it already through
你可能已经通过 GPT 等产品遇到过它，
products like GPT basically intelligence
基本上，智能现在可以
is now available as a service kind of
作为一种服务提供，
like a giant brain floating in the sky
就像漂浮在天空中的巨大大脑一样，
that anyone can talk to
任何人都可以与之交谈
it's not perfect but it is surprisingly capable and it is
它并不完美，但它的能力令人惊讶
improving at an exponential rate this is
并且正在以指数级的速度改进
a big deal it's going to affect just
这是一件大事
about every person and Company on the
它将对地球上的每个人和公司产生
planet positively or negatively this
积极或消极的影响
video is here to help you understand
这段视频旨在帮助您了解
what generative AI is all about in
什么是生成式人工智能
Practical terms beyond the hype
全都是超越炒作的实用术语，
the better you understand this technology as
作为个人团队或公司
a person team or company the better
你对这项技术了解得越多
equipped you will be to survive and
你就越有能力在人工智能时代
thrive in the age of AI so here's a
生存和发展，所以这里有一个
silly but useful mental model for this
愚蠢但有用的心理模型你可以使用，
you have Einstein in your basement
假设每个人的地下室里有一位爱因斯坦
in fact everyone does and by Einstein I
每个人都有
really mean the combination of every
爱因斯坦的真正意思是指
smart person who ever lived
历史上所有聪明人的组合体
you can talk to Einstein whenever you want he has
你可以随时与爱因斯坦交谈
instant access to the sum of all human
而他可以立即访问所有人类知识的总和
knowledge and will answer anything you
并且会在几秒钟内回答
want within seconds never running out of
你想要的任何问题
patience he can also take on any role
永远充满耐心
you want a comedian poet doctor coach
他还可以扮演任何你想要的角色
and will be an expert within that field
喜剧演员、诗人、医生、教练，并成为该领域的专家
he has some human-like limitations though
他也像人类一样存在局限性
he can make mistakes he can jump
他可能会犯错误
to conclusions he can misunderstand you
可能回草率下结论，他可能会误解你
but the biggest limitation is actually
但最大的限制实际上是
your imagination and your ability to
你的想象力以及
communicate effectively with them this
你与他们有效沟通的能力
skill is known as Prompt Engineering and
这种技能被称为“提示词工程”
in the age of AI this is as essential as
在人工智能时代
reading and writing most people vastly
这与阅读和写作一样重要
underestimate what this Einstein in your
大多数人都大大低估了
basement can do it's like going to the
地下室里的爱因斯坦的能力
real Einstein and asking him to proof
就像去问真正的爱因斯坦，请他
read a high school report or hiring a
校对一份高中报告，或者聘请一位
worldclass five-star chef and having him
世界级的五星级厨师让他切洋葱
chop onion the more you interact with
你与爱因斯坦互动越多
Einstein the more you will discover
你就越会发现
surprising and powerful ways for him to
他帮助你或你的公司的
help you or your company okay enough
令人惊讶和强大的手段
fluffy metaphors let's clarify some terms
好吧，让我们澄清一些术语
AI as you probably know stands for
AI，你可能知道它代表“人工智能”
artificial intelligence， AI is not new
AI 并不是什么新鲜事
fields like machine learning and computer
像机器学习和计算机视觉等领域
vision have been around for decades
一样已经存在了几十年
whenever you see a YouTube
每当你看到 YouTube 或B站
recommendation or a web search result or
等视频网站的推荐，或网络搜索结果
whenever you get a credit card
或每当你获批进行信用卡交易时
transaction approved that's traditional
那就是传统的人工智能在工作
AI in action, generative AI is AI that
生成式人工智能是
generates new original content rather
生成新的原始内容的人工智能
than just finding or classifying
而不仅仅是查找或分类现有内容
existing content that's the G in GPT
即 GPT 中的 G(enerative)
for example Large Language Models or LLMs
例如大型语言模型(LLM)
are a type of generative AI that can
是一种生成式人工智能
communicate using normal human language
可以使用普通的人类语言
chatGPT is a product by the company
chatGPT 是 open AI 公司的一款产品，
open AI it started as an LLM essentially
它最初是一个 LLM，本质上是
an advanced chatbot using a new
一个高级聊天机器人，使用一种
architecture called the Transformer
称为 Transformer 架构
architecture which by the way is the T in GPT
的新架构，顺便说一下
it is so fluent at human language
它是 GPT 中的 T，它对人类语言非常流利
that anyone can use it, you don't need to
任何人都可以使用它。而你不需要
be an AI expert or programmer and that's
成为一名人工智能专家或程序员
kind of what triggered the whole Revolution
就是引发整个革命的原因，
so how does it actually work?
那么它实际上如何运作?
well a large language model is an
大语言模型是一个
artificial neural network basically a
人工神经网络，基本上是
bunch of numbers or or parameters
一堆彼此连接的数字或参数，
connected to each other similar to how
类似于我们的大脑
our brain is a bunch of neurons or brain
是一群相互连接的神经元
cells connected to each other neural
或脑细胞，神经网络只处理
networks only deal with numbers you send
您以数字形式发送的
in numbers and depending on how the
数字，并且根据
parameters are set all the numbers come
参数的设置方式，所有数字都会
out but any kind of content such as text
出来，但任何类型的内容（例如文本
or images can be represented as numbers
或图像）都可以表示为数字
so let's say I write dogs are when I
假设我写狗是当我将其
send that to a large language model that
发送到一个大型语言模型时，该模型
gets converted to numbers processed by
会转换为由神经网络处理的数字
the neural network and then the
，然后将
resulting numbers are converted back
结果数字转换
into text in this case the word animals
回文本，在这种情况下，动物这个词
dogs are animals so yeah this is
狗是动物，所以是的，这
basically a guest to next word machine
基本上是 下一个单词机的访客
the interesting part is if we take that
有趣的部分是，如果我们获取该
output and combine it with the input and
输出并将其与输入结合起来并
send it through the model again then it
再次通过模型发送它，那么它将
will continue adding new words that's
继续添加新单词，这就是
what's going on behind the scenes when
当
you type something in chat GPT in this
您在聊天 GPT 中键入内容时幕后发生的事情
case for example it generated a whole
例如，在这种情况下，它生成了一个完整的
story and I can continue this
故事，我可以
indefinitely by adding more
通过添加更多提示无限期地继续下去
prompts a large language model may have
大型语言模型可能有数
billions or even trillions of of
十亿甚至数万亿个
parameters that's why they're called
参数，这就是它们被称为
large so how are all these numbers set
大型的原因，那么所有这些数字如何
well not through manual programming that
不通过手动设置好 编程是
would be impossible but through training
不可能的，但通过训练
just like babies learning to speak a
就像婴儿学习说话一样，
baby isn't told how to speak she doesn't
婴儿没有被告知如何说话，她没有
get an instruction manual instead she
指导手册，而是
listens to people speaking around her
听周围的人说话
and when she's heard enough she starts
，当她听得足够多时，她开始
seeing the pattern she speaks a few
看到她的模式 首先会说几个
words at first to the Delight of her
单词让她的
parents and then later on full sentences
父母高兴，然后在训练期间类似地说出完整的句子，
similarly during a training period the
language model is fed a mindboggling
语言模型会被输入
amount of text to learn from Mostly from
大量的文本来学习，主要来自
internet sources it then plays guess the
互联网来源，然后它会用
next word with all of this over and over
所有的信息来猜测下一个单词。 一遍又一遍，
again and the parameters are
参数会
automatically tweaked until it starts
自动调整，直到它开始
getting really good at predicting the
真正擅长预测下一个
next word this is called back
单词，这称为反向
propagation which is a fancy term for oh
传播，这是一个奇特的术语，哦，
I guessed wrong I better change
我猜错了，我最好改变
something however to become truly useful
一些东西，但是要变得真正有用​​，
a model also needs to undergo human
模型还需要 接受人类
training this is called reinforcement
训练，这被称为
learning with human feedback and it
带有人类反馈的强化学习，它
involves thousands of hours of humans
涉及人类数千小时的
painstakingly testing and evaluating
艰苦测试和评估
output from the model and giving
模型的输出，并提供
feedback kind of like training a a dog
反馈，就像
with a clicker to reinforce good
用答题器训练狗来强化良好
behavior that's why a model like GPT
行为一样，这就是为什么像 GPT 这样的模型
won't tell you how to rob a bank it
不会告诉你如何抢劫银行，它
knows very well how to rob a bank but
非常清楚如何抢劫银行，但
through human training it has learned
通过人类训练，它知道
that it shouldn't help people commit
它不应该帮助人们
crimes when training is done the model
犯罪，当训练完成时，模型
is mostly Frozen other than some fine
大部分被冻结，除了一些微调之外
tuning that can happen later that's what
稍后可能会发生，这就是
the P stands for in GPT pre-trained
GPT 预训练中的 P 代表的意思，
although in the future we will probably
尽管将来我们可能会
have models that can learn continuously
拥有可以连续学习的模型，而
rather than just uh during training and
不仅仅是在训练和
fine-tuning now although chat GPT kind
微调期间呃，尽管聊天 GPT
of got the ball rolling GPT isn't the
有点让球滚动 GPT 不是'
only model out there in fact new models
事实上，新的模型正在
are sprouting like
像
mushrooms they vary a lot in terms of
蘑菇一样涌现，它们在
speed capability and cost some can be
速度能力和成本方面差异很大，有些可以
downloaded and run locally others are
下载并在本地运行，有些
only online some are free or open source
只能在线，有些是免费或开源的，
others are commercial products some are
有些是商业产品，有些
super easy to use While others require
非常简单 虽然其他需要
complicated technical setup some are
复杂的技术设置，但有些
specialized for certain use cases others
专门用于某些用例，其他
are more General and can be used for
则更通用，几乎可以用于
almost anything and some are baked into
任何东西，有些以
products in the form of co-pilots or or
副驾驶或
chat windows it's it's the Wild West
聊天窗口的形式融入产品中，这就是狂野西部，
just keep in mind that you generally get
只是保留 请记住，
what you pay for so with a free model
一分钱一分货，因此使用免费模型，
you may just be getting a smart high
您可能只是在地下室找到一个聪明的
school student in your basement rather
高中生，而
than Einstein the difference between for
不是爱因斯坦。
example GPT 3.5 and GPT 4 is massive
例如，GPT 3.5 和 GPT 4 之间的区别是巨大的，请
note that there are different types of
注意，有不同类型的模型
generative AI models that generate
生成不同类型内容的生成 AI 模型
different types of content textto text
models like gpc4 take text as input and
像 gpc4 这样的文本到文本模型将文本作为输入并
generate text as output the text can be
生成文本作为输出 文本可以是
natural language but it can also be
自然语言，但也可以是
structured information like code Json
结构化信息，例如代码 Json
HTML I use this a lot myself to generate
HTML 我自己经常使用它来生成
code when programming uh it saves an
代码 编程呃，它节省了
incredible amount of time and I also
大量的时间，我还
learn a lot from the code it generates
从代码中学到了很多东西，它生成
text to image models will generate
文本到图像模型，将生成
images describe what you want and an
图像描述你想要的内容，并
image gets generated for you you can
为你生成图像，你
even pick a style image to image models
甚至可以选择一种风格图像到图像模型
can do things like transforming or
可以做的事情 诸如转换或
combining images and we have image to
组合图像之类的事情，我们有图像到
text models which describe the contents
文本模型，用于描述给
of a given image and speech to text
定图像的内容，而语音到文本模型则
models create voice transcriptions which
创建语音转录，这
is useful for things like uh meeting
对于诸如会议记录文本之类的事情很有用。音频模型，
notes text Audio models they generate
它们
music or sounds from a prompt for
根据提示生成音乐或声音。
example here is some sound generated
例如，这里是从提示中生成的一些声音，
from The Prompt people talking in a
人们在忙碌中说话，
busy okay guys enough stop now thank you
好吧，现在停下来，谢谢，
and there are even text to video models
甚至还有文本到视频模型，可以根据
that generate videos from a prompt
提示生成视频，
sooner or later we'll have infinite
迟早我们将拥有无限的
movie series that autog generate the
电影系列，自动生成
next episode tailored to your tastes as
下一个 根据您的口味量身定制的剧集，因为
you're watching kind of scary if you
您正在观看，如果您
think about it one Trend now is
考虑一下，有点可怕现在的一个趋势是
multimodal AI products meaning they
多模式人工智能产品，这意味着它们将
combine different models into one
不同的模型组合到一个
product so you can work with text images
产品中，这样您就可以处理文本图像
audio Etc without switching tools the
音频等，而无需切换工具
chat GPT mobile app is a good example of
聊天GPT移动应用程序 这是一个很好的例子，
this just for fun I took a photo of this
只是为了好玩，我给这个房间拍了一张照片，
room and I asked where I could hide
我问我可以把东西藏在哪里，
stuff I kind of like that it mentioned
我有点喜欢它提到了
the stove but warned that that it could
炉子，但警告说，
get hot there when I have things to
当我有事情要弄清楚时，那里可能会很热。
figure out such as the contents of this
正如本视频的内容一样，
video I like to take walks using chat
我喜欢使用聊天
GPT as as a sounding board I start by
GPT 作为共鸣板来散步，我首先会
saying always respond with the word okay
说，总是用“好的”这个词来回答，
unless I ask you for something that way
除非我向你询问什么，这样在
it'll just listen and not interrupt
after I finish dumping my thoughts I ask
我倾倒完我的东西后，它就会只是听而不打扰。 我
for feedback we have some discussion and
请求反馈，我们进行了一些讨论，
then I ask it to summarize and text
然后我要求它进行总结和文字处理，我
afterwards I really recommend trying
真的建议尝试一下，这
this it's it's a really useful way to
是使用这样的工具的一种非常有用的方法，事实
use tools like this turns out Einstein
证明爱因斯坦并
isn't stuck in the basement after all
没有被困在地下室里，毕竟
you can take him out for a walk
你可以采取一切措施 他出去散步
initially language models were just word
最初，语言模型只是文字
predictors statistical machines with
预测统计机器，
limited practical use but as they became
实际用途有限，但随着它们变得越来越
larger and were trained on more data
大，接受了更多数据的训练，
they started gaining emergent
它们开始获得新兴的
capabilities expected capabilities that
能力，预期的能力
surprised even the developers of the
甚至让技术开发人员感到惊讶，
technology they could roleplay write
他们可以角色扮演
poetry write high quality code discuss
写诗写 高质量的代码讨论
company strategy provide legal and
公司战略提供法律和
medical advice coach teach basically
医疗建议教练教授基本上
creative and intellectual things that
创造性和智力的东西，这些东西
only humans could do previously it turns
以前只有人类才能做到，事实
out that when a model has seen enough
证明，当模型看到足够的
text and images it starts to see
文本和图像时，它开始看到
patterns and understand higher level
模式并理解更高层次的
Concepts just like a baby learning to
概念，就像一个模型一样。 宝贝学习
understand the world let's take a simple
理解世界 让我们举一个简单的
example I'll give gpc4 this little
例子 我会给 gpc4 这张小
drawing that involves a string a pair of
图，其中包括一根绳子 一把
scissors an egg a pot and a fire what
剪刀 一个鸡蛋 一个锅和一把火
will happen if I use the scissors the
如果我使用剪刀会发生什么
model has most likely not been trained
模型很可能没有经过训练
on this exact scenario yet it gave a
在这个确切的场景中，它给出了一个
pretty good answer which demonstrates a
很好的答案，展示了对
basic understanding of the nature of
scissors eggs gravity and heat when GPT
GPT 4 发布时剪刀蛋重力和热量性质的基本理解
4 was released I started using it as a
我开始使用它作为
coding assistant and I was blown away
编码助手，
when prompted effectively it was a
当有效提示时我感到震惊，它是一个
better programmer than anyone I've
更好的 程序员比我共事过的任何人都更擅长
worked with same with article writing
撰写
product design Workshop planning and
产品设计研讨会规划，而
just about anything I used it for for
我用它来解决
the main bottleneck was my prompt
主要瓶颈的任何事情都是我的即时
engineering skills so I decided to make
工程技能，所以我决定进行
a career shift and focus entirely on
职业转变，完全专注于
learning and teaching how to make this
学习和教授如何 让这项
technology useful hence this video now
技术变得有用，因此现在这个视频让
let's take a step back and look at the
我们退后一步，看看大约
implications for 300,000 years or so we
30 万年以来我们
homosapiens have been the most
智人一直是
intelligent species on Earth depending
地球上最聪明的物种，这
of course on how you define intelligence
当然取决于你如何定义智力，
but the thing is our intellectual
但问题是我们的智力
capabilities aren't really improving
能力并不高。
that much our brains are about the same
我们的大脑并没有真正改善那么多，与
size same weight as they've been for
它们几千年来的大小和重量差不多，
thousands of years computers on the
other hand have been around for only 80
另一方面，计算机只出现了 80
years or so and now with generative AI
年左右，现在有了生成式人工智能，
they are suddenly capable of speaking
它们突然能够说
human languages fluently and carrying
人类语言了 流利地
out an increasing number of intellectual
执行越来越多
creative tasks that previously only
以前只有
humans could do so we are right here at
人类才能完成的智力创造性任务，所以我们正处于
the Crossing Point where AI is better at
交叉点，人工智能在
some things and humans are better at
某些事情上做得更好，人类在
some things but ai's capabilities are
某些事情上做得更好，但人工智能的能力正在
improving at an exponential rate while
以指数级速度提高，而
ours aren't we don't know how long that
我们的不是，我们不知道这种
exponential Improvement will continue or
指数级的进步会持续多久，或者
if it will level off at some point but
是否会在某个时候趋于平稳，但
we're definitely entering a new world
我们肯定正在进入一个新的世界
order now this isn't the first
秩序，这不是
Revolution we've experienced we tamed
我们经历的第一次革命，我们驯服了
fire we learned how to do agriculture we
火 我们学会了如何从事农业 我们
invented the printing press steam power
发明了印刷机 蒸汽动力
Telegraph these were all revolutionary
电报 这些都是革命性的
changes but they took decades or
变化，但它们花了几十年或几个
centuries to become widespread in the AI
世纪才在人工智能
Revolution new technology spreads
革命中广泛传播 新技术
worldwide almost instantly dealing with
几乎立即传播到全世界 处理
this rate of change is a huge challenge
这种变化速度对双方来说都是一个巨大的挑战
for both individuals and
个人和
companies I've noticed that people and
公司我注意到，当谈到人工智能时，人们和
companies tend to fall into different
公司往往会陷入不同的
kind of mindset categories when it comes
思维类别，
to AI on one side we have denial the
一方面我们否认
belief that AI cannot do my job or we
人工智能无法完成我的工作，或者我们
don't have time to look into this
没有时间研究这一点
technology this is a dangerous place to
技术这是一个危险的地方，
be a common saying is AI might not take
俗话说，人工智能可能不会抢走
your job but people using AI will and
你的工作，但使用人工智能的人会，
this is true for both individuals and
这对于天平另一边的个人和公司来说都是如此，
companies on the other side of the scale
we have panic and despair the belief
我们对人工智能正在消失的信念感到恐慌和绝望
that AI is going to take my job no
接受我的工作，
matter what AI is going to make my
无论人工智能会让我的
company go bankrupt neither of these
公司破产，这两种
mindsets are helpful so I propose a
心态都没有帮助，所以我提出了一个
middle ground a balanced positive
中间立场，一种平衡的积极
mindset AI is going to make me my team
心态，人工智能将使我，我的团队，
my company insanely productive
我的公司，
personally with this mindset I feel like
个人以这种心态变得非常高效。 就像
I've gained superpowers I can go from
我获得了超能力一样，我可以
idea to result in so much shorter time I
在更短的时间内从想法到结果，我
can focus more on what I want to achieve
可以更多地专注于我想要实现的目标，
and less on the grunt workk of building
而不是构建东西的繁重工作，
things and I'm learning a lot faster too
而且我学得也更快，
it's like having an awesome Mentor with
就像拥有一个 很棒的导师一直在
me at all times this mindset not only
我身边，这种心态不仅
feels good but it also equips you for
感觉很好，而且还为你的
the future makes you less likely to lose
未来做好了准备，使你不太可能失去
your job or your company and more likely
工作或公司，并且更有可能
to thrive in the age of AI despite all
在人工智能时代蓬勃发展，尽管存在所有
the
uncertainty so one important question is
不确定性，所以有一个重要的问题 这
is human role X needed in the age of AI
是人工智能时代需要的人类角色X，
for example are doctors needed
例如，需要医生、
developers lawyers CEOs uh whatever so
开发人员、律师、首席执行官，嗯，无论如何，随着
this question becomes more and more
relevant as the AI capabilities improve
人工智能能力的提高，这个问题变得越来越相关，
well some jobs will disappear for sure
有些工作肯定会消失，
but for most roles I think we humans are
但对于大多数角色，我认为我们人类是
still needed someone with domain
仍然需要具有领域
knowledge still needs to decide what to
知识的人仍然需要决定向
ask the AI how to formulate The Prompt
人工智能提出
what context needs to be provided and
什么问题如何制定提示需要提供什么上下文以及
how to evaluate the result AI models
如何评估结果人工智能模型
aren't perfect they can be absolutely
并不完美他们有时可能非常
brilliant sometimes but sometimes also
聪明但有时也
terribly stupid they can sometimes
非常愚蠢他们 有时会
hallucinate and provide bogus
产生幻觉并
information in a very convincing way so
以非常令人信服的方式提供虚假信息，因此
when should you trust the AI response
您何时应该信任人工智能响应
when should you double check or do the
何时应该仔细检查或
work yourself what about legal
自己完成工作法律
compliance data security what
合规性数据安全性
information can we send to an AI model
我们可以向人工智能模型发送哪些信息
and where is that data stored a human
以及该数据在哪里
expert is needed to make these judgment
需要人类专家来做出这些
calls and compensate for the weaknesses
判断并弥补
of the AI model so I recommend thinking
人工智能模型的弱点，所以我建议将
of AI as your colleague a genius but
人工智能视为你的同事，一个天才，但
also an oddball with some personal
也是一个有一些个人
quirks that you need to learn to work
怪癖的怪人，你需要学习与
with you need to recognize when your
你一起工作 作为
Genius colleague is drunk as a doctor my
一名医生，我的
AI colleague can help diagnose rare
人工智能同事可以帮助诊断
diseases that I didn't even know existed
我什至不知道的罕见疾病的存在
as a lawyer my AI colleague could do
作为一名律师，我的人工智能同事可以进行
legal research and review contracts
法律研究并审查合同，
allowing me to spend more time with my
让我可以花更多时间与
client or as a teacher my AI colleague
客户相处，或者作为一名律师 老师，我的 AI 同事
could grade tests help generate course
可以对测试进行评分，帮助生成课程
content provide individual support to
内容，为学生提供个人支持
students Etc and if you're not sure how
等等，如果您不确定
it can help you just ask it I work as X
它如何帮助您，只需询问它，我作为 X 工作，
how can you help me overall I find that
您总体上如何帮助我，我发现
the combination of human plus AI That's
人类的结合 加人工智能这就是
where the magic lies it's important to
神奇之处，
distinguish between the models and the
区分模型和
products that build on top of them as a
构建在模型之上的产品非常重要，作为
user you don't normally interact with
用户，您通常不会
the model directly instead you interact
直接与模型交互，而是
with a product website or a mobile app
与产品网站或移动应用程序交互，而产品网站或移动应用程序又
which in turn talks to the model behind
与幕后模型对话
the scenes products provide a user
产品提供用户
interface and add capabilities and data
界面并添加
that aren't part of the model itself for
不属于模型本身的功能和数据，
example the chat gbt product keeps track
例如聊天 GBT 产品会跟踪
of your message history while the GPT 4
您的消息历史记录，而 GPT 4
model itself doesn't have any message
模型本身没有任何消息
history history as a developer you can
作为开发人员的历史，您可以
use these models to build your own AI
使用这些模型来构建自己的人工智能
powered products and features for
产品和功能，
example let's say you have an e-learning
例如，假设您有一个电子学习
site you could add a chat bot to answer
网站，您可以添加一个聊天机器人来回答
questions about the courses or as a
有关课程的问题，或者作为
recruitment company you might build AI
您可能建立的招聘公司 AI
powered tools to help evaluate
支持的工具可帮助评估
candidates in both these cases your
候选人，在这两种情况下，您的
users interact with your product and
用户与您的产品交互，
then your product interacts with the
然后您的产品与
model this is done via apis or
模型交互，这是通过 API 或应用程序编程接口完成的，这些接口
application programming interfaces which
allow your code to talk to the model so
允许您的代码与模型对话，所以
here's a simple example of using open AI
这里是一个使用的简单示例 开放AI
API to talk to GP
API与GP交谈
not a lot of code needed and here's
不需要很多代码，这是
another example of the automatic
candidate evaluation thing I talked
我谈到的自动候选人评估的另一个例子，
about it takes a job description and a
它需要一个职位描述和
bunch of CVS in a folder and evaluates
文件夹中的一堆CVS，并
each candidate automatically and
自动评估每个候选人，顺便说一句，
incidentally the code itself is mostly
代码本身是 主要是
AI written as a product developer you
作为产品开发人员编写的人工智能，你
can use AI models kind of like an
可以使用人工智能模型，就像
external brain to insert intelligence
外部大脑一样，将智能插入
into your product very powerful in order
到你的产品中，非常强大，
to use generative AI effectively you
为了有效地使用生成式人工智能，你
need to get good at prompt engineering
需要擅长即时工程
or prompt design as I prefer to call it
或即时设计，我更喜欢这样称呼它
this skill is needed both as a user and
作为用户和
as a product developer because in both
产品开发人员都需要这项技能，因为在这两种
cases you need to be able to craft
情况下，您都需要能够制作
effective prompts that produce useful
有效的提示，
results from an AI model here's an
从人工智能模型中产生有用的结果，这里有一个
example let's say I want help planning a
例子，假设我需要帮助规划一个
workshop this prompt is unlikely to give
研讨会，这个提示不太可能实现 给出
useful results because no matter how
有用的结果，因为无论
smart the AI is if it doesn't know the
人工智能有多聪明，如果它不知道
context of my workshop it can only give
我的研讨会的背景，它只能
fague high level recommendations the
给出高水平的建议
second prompt is better now I provided
第二个提示更好，现在我提供了
some context this is normally done
一些背景，这通常是迭代完成的，
iteratively write a prompt look at the
写一个提示看看
result add a follow-up prompt to provide
结果添加一个后续提示以提供
more information or edit the original
更多信息或编辑原始
prompt and rinse and repeat until you
提示并冲洗并重复，直到您
get a good result in this third approach
在第三种方法中获得良好的结果，
I ask it to interview me so instead of
我要求它采访我，所以
me providing a bunch of context up front
我不需要预先提供一堆上下文，
I'm basically saying what do you need to
我' 我基本上是说你需要
know in order order to help me and then
知道什么才能帮助我，然后在
it will propose a workshop agenda after
I often combine these two I provide a
我经常将这两者结合起来之后，它会提出一个研讨会议程，我提供
bit of context and then I tell it to ask
一些背景信息，然后我告诉它询问
me if it needs any more information
我是否需要更多信息
these are just some examples of prompt
这些 这些只是即时工程技术的一些示例，
engineering techniques so overall the
因此总的来说，
better you get at prompt engineering the
您在即时工程方面做得越好，
faster and better results you will get
您从人工智能中获得的结果就越快、越好，有
from AI there are plenty of courses
很多课程、
books videos articles to help you learn
书籍、视频文章可以帮助您学习
this but the most important thing is is
这一点，但最重要的是
to practice and Learn by doing a nice
练习和 通过做学习的一个很好的
side effect is that you will become
副作用是，你会变得
better at communicating in general since
更好地沟通，因为
prompt engineering is really all about
及时的工程实际上都是关于
Clarity and effective
清晰度和有效的
communication I think the next Frontier
沟通，我认为
for generative AI is autonomous agents
生成人工智能的下一个前沿是带有工具的自主代理，
with tools these are AI powerered
这些工具是人工智能驱动的
software entities that run on their own
软件实体，运行在 他们自己的，
rather than just sitting around waiting
而不是只是坐在那里等待
for you to prompt them all the time so
你一直提示他们，所以
you go down to Einstein in your basement
你去地下室的爱因斯坦那里，
and do what a good leader would do for a
做一个好的领导者会为团队做的事情，
team you give him a high level Mission
你给他一个高水平的使命
and the tools needed to accomplish it
和完成它所需的工具
and then open the door and let him out
然后打开门，让他出去
to run his own show without
运行自己的节目，无需进行
micromanagement the tools could be
微观管理。工具可以是
things like access to the internet
诸如访问互联网、
access to money ability to send and
访问金钱、发送和
receive messages order pizza or whatever
接收消息、订购披萨或其他任何东西，
for this prompt engineering becomes even
对于这种即时工程来说，变得
more important because your autonomous
更加重要，因为你的自主性
tool wielding agent can do a lot of good
工具挥舞代理可以做很多好事
or a lot of harm depending on how well
或很多坏事，这取决于
you craft that mission
你如何制定使命
statement all right let's wrap it up
宣言好吧，让我们把它总结
here are the key things I hope you will
在这里是我希望你能从
remember from this video generative AI
这个视频中记住的关键事情生成人工智能
is a super useful tool that can help
是一个超级有用的工具 可以
both you your team and your company in a
在很大程度上帮助你、你的团队和你的公司，
big way the better you understand it the
你对它了解得越多，
more likely it is to be an opportunity
它就越有可能成为一个机会，而不是一个
rather than a threat generative AI is
威胁。人工智能比
more powerful than you think the biggest
你想象的更强大，最大的
limitation is not the technology but
限制不是技术，而是
your imagination like what can I do and
你的想象力，比如 我能做什么以及
your prompt engineering skills how do I
你的即时工程技能 我该怎么
do it prompt engineeringdesign is a
做 即时工程设计是一项
crucial skill like all new skills just
至关重要的技能，就像所有新技能一样，只要
accept that you will kind of suck at it
接受你一开始会有点烂的事实，
at first but you'll improve over time
但随着时间的推移，你会
with deliberate practice so my best tip
通过刻意练习而提高，所以我最好的建议 这
is experiment make this part of your
是一个实验，使这成为您
day-to-day life and the Learning Happens
日常生活的一部分，并且学习会
automatically hope this video was
自动发生希望该视频对您有所
helpful thanks for
帮助，感谢
[Music]
watching
观看[音乐]